

Marcus Napoleon Lising

marcusnapoleon.com

416.554.2793 : marcus.napoleon@bell.net

1817 - 77 Howard Street, Toronto, ON M4X-1J9

Summary:

I am a self-taught web developer, with keen interest and passion to continually learn and grow. I am currently seeking a new challenge and career path in a Frontend Web developer role in an environment where mentoring of junior developers is part of the culture, to keep them encouraged in learning to further build and improve their skills.

While I possess no professional experience in the web development industry, I bring soft skills, customer service skills developed over 15 years of background in various levels and types of customer/client facing services, 7 years of which are in the IT industry, technical/client support.

Skills:

- Web Development
 - HTML
 - CSS
 - JavaScript
 - Node
 - AJAX
- Web Design
 Figma
- CMS
 - WordPress
 - Drupal 7
- Google Analytics
- Technical Support
- · Client/Customer Service
- Active Learning
- · Critical Thinking

Social Media:

in /marcuslising

(<u>*</u>) /marcusnapoleon

/marcusnapoleon

G Marcus Lising

Education:

Google Analytics for Beginners

Google Analytics Academy

- · Basic features
- Account creation
- Tracking Code integration
- · Basic report analysis
- · Goals and Campaigns tracking set up

Complete JavaScript - Jonas Schmedtmann

Udemy.com

- JavaScript Fundamentals
- ES6
- 00P
- AJAX
- Node

Responsive Web Design

freeCodeCamp

- HTML/HTML5
- CSS/CSS3
- · Design Fundamentals
- Responsive Design

OCD - Computer Systems Technician (T141)

George Brown College Casa Loma Campus

- Course Concentration Networking (CCNA)
- GPA 3.3
- Graduated with Honors
- Dean's List Recipient 2 Semesters
- Peer Leader/Tutor/Lab TA

May 2019

Menlo Park, CA

April 2019

San Francisco, CA

January 2019 San Francisco, CA

April 2011 Toronto, Canada

Experience:

TELAX - Hosted Call Center

May 2017 - Dec 2018

Technical/Client Support (Remote)

Toronto, ON

- First point of contact for Customer Support for the Telax Hosted Call Center software solution and the customer facing operation.
- Cooperatively communicating with the Operations and Engineering group for continuous maintenance and monitoring of the Hosted Service infrastructure.
- Communicating and coordinating with client Technical and Engineering group, vendors and third party groups when
 performing MACD of Telax provided VoIP, apps, and services.

Canadian National Institute for the Blind (CNIB)

Nov 2013 - Oct 2016

Client Support Technician (Contract)

Toronto, ON

- Covering a broad range of duties, with emphasis on the technical assistance/support of CNIB print disabled library clients using the direct-to-player Internet-delivered service.
- Acting as the second level contact for users/clients with service issues that cannot be resolved by the CNIB National Helpline (call centre) staff.

Projects/Achievements

- Tasked to plan/design/build a service/donation configuration request form using Drupal 7.
- Tasked to plan/deploy a nationwide brand specific Daisy Player firmware upgrade, a 2/3 step process ensuring that all CNIB deployed players are updated with the same firmware version.
- Tasked to Plan/establish the Client Support Technician Dept. Client Handling Operations and Procedures.

SNC-Lavalin Group

Jun 2012 - May 2013

OTL Support L-2

Etobicoke, ON

- Provide 1st and 2nd level National Oracle T&L Support (Vancouver, Calgary, Winnipeg, Sarnia, Oakville, and Toronto BU's).
- Respond to client calls and emails regarding Oracle T&L related issues (Timesheets, Expense Reports, Oracle Access and Responsibilities, Workflow Errors).
- Work in cooperation with HR Payroll Benefits Dept., Finance Dept., BUC's, Oracle Level 3 support (Montreal) and/or IT Department to resolve issues in a timely manner.

Projects/Achievements

- Received plaque of appreciation for involvement and support of the SNC-Lavalin Calgary Hydrocarbons and Chemicals
 Oracle implementation.
- Resolved and closed 95% of received Oracle T&L Level1&2 tickets.

SNC-Lavalin Group

March 2012 - Jun 2012

Service Desk Analyst/OTL Support L-1

Etobicoke, ON

OTL Support

- Provide 1st level Oracle T&L support, responding to client calls and emails regarding their Oracle T&L accounts and timesheet issues as well as user expense report issues.
- Create/Reset user Oracle accounts and password.

Service Desk Analyst

- Provide user assistance and technical support for PC, LAN, and application products (both in-house and package).
- Respond to client calls and emails regarding IT related issues.